Kheel, Theodore W. Additional Files. 6021/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Queens Surface Corp. + TWU, Local 100 Gino Durso + Keith Hall, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Aug 23
- Queens Surface Corp. TWU Local 100 1. Minichello 2. Schweit, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Queens surface corp. TWU, Local 100 Charles McCall, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  April 25
- Queens surface TWU Local 100 Rhonda Miller, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Queens Surface Corp. TWU Local 100 1. Charisse Gray 2. R Franco E Milano, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Queens surface Corp. TWU Local 100 Edward Milano, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  March 30
- Queens surface Corp. Semmick, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  May 31
- Queens surface Corp. TWU Local 100 1. John colon 2. Keith Hall, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Jan 4
- Tufaro Transportation Frank Dionofrio, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Aug 19
- Rainbow Transportation ATU Local 1181-1061 Nathaniel Torres, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  March 21
- ATU local 1181-1061, Rainbow Transit Donald Ambrose + Maude Theodore, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Arbitration: Rainbow Transit + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Edna Devallon, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Jan 10
- ATU Local 1181-1061 rainbow Carry Kid - Edna Devallon/Maude Theodore/ Vionette Rodriguez (Box 7, Folder 13)
- rainbow Trans. Co. ATU local 1181-1061 James Singleton, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Aug. 28
- rainbow Transit Ira Rosen ATU Local 1181-1061 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Nov 17
- Arbitration Files ATU local 1181-1061, Rainbow Transit - Pierre Fenelus (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Arbitration files CIFRA Escorts - Re: Lenora Upsher, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Rainbow Transit + ATU Local 1181-1061 Julio Echevarria, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Triboro coach Corp. TWU Local 100 Re. Summer Pick of runs, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  June 28
- Triboro coach TWU Local 100 Miguel Velez, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  March 22
- Triboro coach Corp. Christopher Matthews, Isaac Bougas, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Aug 28
- Triboro Coach Corp. TWU, Local 100 Claude L. Hudson, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Triboro coach corp. TWU Local 100 John O'Neil, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Feb 4
- triboro Coach corp. - Letter from Kheel Records, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Arbitration files ATU Local 1181-1061, USA United Bus Express - Typhone Chisolm, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  March 17
- United Bus Express + ATU Local 1181-1061, AFL-CIO Victor Gonzalez, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  March 18
- United fleet + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Nicomedes Molina, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- United School Bus + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Herve Lecoin, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Aug 29
- Arbitration files ATU Local 1181-1061, United Trans - Tynerts Milfort, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Arbitration files ATU Local 1181-1061, United Transit - Dickens F. Charles, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Varsity Transit + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Woodrow Abbott, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Varsity Transit + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Choute, Wasenbeck, Alexander, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Feb 21
- Varsity Transit + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Raymond LaRoche, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- varsity Transit + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Richard Downes, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  June 18
- Varsity Transit + ATU, Local 1181-1061 Charles Morivil, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Liberty Lines Calvin Cuttino, TWU Local 100 Richard Finch, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  Oct 2
- Liberty Lines Express - TWU Local 100 Frank Baylor, Rosario, Wharton, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Liberty Lines - Baylor (Folder 2) (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Barney Smyth Liberty, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Dec 4
- Liberty Lines Walter Arujo, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Oct 4
- Liberty Lines Samuel Patterson, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Liberty Lines + Liberty Express Contract Dispute - Layoff + Pay Reduction, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Dec 29
- association for the Study of abortion,, Inc. 6076-1 correspondence + Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. 6076-2 Minutes and Agendas, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. 6076-3 Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. 6076-4 Corporate Papers, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. 6076-5 Duplicates and Drafts, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. 6076- Personnel Practices, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Association for the Study of abortion, Inc. 6076-7 reports, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Distance Learning files - Association of Joint Labor/Management educational Programs Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Association of Joint Labor/Management Educational Programs - distance Learning Files Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Association of Joint Labor/ Management Educational Programs - distance Learning files correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Association of Joint Labor/Management Education Programs - distance Learning Files Conference Programs, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Association of Joint Labor/Management Education Programs - distance Learning Files Minutes of Meetings + Conference Calls (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Association of Joint Labor/Management educational Programs Board of director Meeting -, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  June 30
- Association of Joint Labor/Management educational Programs Pocket from, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  May 11
- Association of Joint Labor/ Management Educational Programs Board of Directors Meeting. Briefing Book, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Feb 23
- Association of Joint/Labor Management Education Programs - Bd of Dir Meeting, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Oct 17
- Distance Learning Files - Assoc. of Joint Labor/Management Education Programs Foundation Corporate Documents (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Distance Learning Files - Association of Joint Labor/Management Education Programs Sales Agreement between World Internet Resources, Inc. and Joint Labor association (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Distance Learning Files - Assoc. of Joint Labor/ Management Education Programs CWA/Comcast, 2003-2005 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Distance Learning Files - Assoc. of Joint Labor/ Management Education Programs Laws and Regulations for Union Members, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Association of Joint Labor - Management Educational Programs - Newsletters + Brochure, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Assoc. of Joint Labor/Management Educational Programs - distance Learning Beta-Test, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Association of Joint Labor/ Management Ed. Programs - distance Learning - Adult Workers Research Project, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Oct
- Distance Learning - Center for Lifelong Ed Corporate Records, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  July
- The Alliance/Distance Learning Marshall Goldberg, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- The Alliance/distance Learning (Marshall coldberg) Dell: Mission Statement, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- The alliance/Distance Learning (Marshall Goldberg) Remarks by Morton Bahr, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- The Alliance / Distance Learning (Marshall Goldberg) Experiments in Distance Learning - correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- The Alliance/Distance Learning (Marshall Goldberg) correspondence with Morton Bahr, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Athlone Industries Annual report, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Athlone Industries, Inc. Questionnaire forms, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Athlone Industries RE: Jessop Steel Company/Green river Steel Corporation Pension Plan - Nov. 1981, Redweld #2 out of 2 (Folder 1) (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Athlone Industries Re: Jessop Steel company/Green River Steel Corporation Plan - Nov. 1981, Redweld #2 out of 2 (folder 2) (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Athlone Industries Re: Jessop Steel company/Green River Steel Corporation Pension Plan - Nov. 1981, Redweld #2 out of 2 (folder 3) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Athlone Industries - Nebenzahl v. Miller, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Athlone Industries, Nebenzahl v. Miller, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Automation House - General, 1968-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Automation House - general Correspondence File (x-ref: CNB correspondence File), 1982-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Automation House - Lewis Mumford/PBS, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Automation House - Miscellaneous, 1965-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Automation house - Sale to Dorazio contract of Sale, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Automation House - TCF Mortgage Loan Closing Documents, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Automation House - TCF Mortgage Loan Extra Copies, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment Property Tax Cases, Exemption Application, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment TWK Statement 1967-1972 Property Tax memo of Law (Box 10, Folder 9)
- automation House (CNB-TV) Drafts/Duplicates, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- American Foundation on automation + Employment - foundation on Automation + Human Development, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- American Foundation on automation + employment - Proposal for Center for the Advancement of National Manpower Goals, 1969- 1970 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Israel conference Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Automation house - Correspondence joseph Krevisky Memos, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment Inc. Israel conference Information bulletin, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Israel conference Program, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Israel Conference Lists of Participants, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Israel conference Conference Papers, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Israel Conference Summary of conference (Monthly Labor Review), 1968- 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Israel Conference Miscellaneous Handwritten Notes, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Israel Conference Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Automation House - Asmudsson/Taittinger Matter (General), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Automation House - Asmudsson/Taittinger Matter Agreement of Lease, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Automation House - Asmudsson/Taittinger Matter Memorandum of Understanding, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Automation house - Asmudsson/taittinger Matter CNB v. AVTS Inc. (Amaury Taittinger) complaint, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- automation House - Asmudsson/Taittinger Matter CNB v. AVTS, Deposition of TW Kheel (Box 10, Folder 26)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment Inc. - Crossed Wires, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Foundation of Automation and Employment Automation House (CNB-TV) Penn-York Construction corp. (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Automation House - CNBT Proposal for Grant (Helen Rubenstein foundation), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- automation House Sterling Manhattan Cable Television, Inc.. 1971 Correspondence RE: A.H. Video Facilities (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Automation House - Technology, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Automation House - Collective Bargaining Forum, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment The Magic Theatre, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Automation house - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- automation House - Alosco Proposal, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Automation House - Mittleman Matter, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Automation House Form of Lease Agreement between 39 E. 68th + Saxe, Bacon, + Bolan, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Automation House Draft Papers RE: Sale with Mortgage Papers (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Automation House - Certificate of Occupancy, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- automation House Larry Wiessman (Ricci Matter), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- automation House Mortgage (guarantee of Payment), 1967-1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Automation House Appraisal, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- automation House Building Alteration, 1967-1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Automation house Plans, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- PIPR Services May 1 - Oct 31 1979 (PR) (Public Interest Public Relations) (Box 11, Folder 14)
- automation House, CNB-TV, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- automation House (CNB-TV) Minutes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- American Foundation on Automation and Employment, Inc. Correspondence, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Foundation of Automation and Employment Correspondence, 1968-1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Foundation of Automation and Employment, Inc. Correspondence and Memoranda Vol. VIII, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Foundation of Automation and Employment, Inc. Correspondence + Memoranda Vol. VII, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- foundation for Automation and Employment - Climbing the Job Ladder Publication, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Automation House (CNB-TV) thomas C. Lehrecke, Architect, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Foundation on Automation and Employment Inc., 1968-1976 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Other Related Companies - Global Botanix Corp., 1999 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Other Related Companies - business Enterprises for sustainable Travel (The conference Board), 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Other Related Companies - RE: Global Ceuticals Corp., 1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Other Related Companies - the National Tropical Botanical Garden / Nat'l Library for Tropical Plants + Forestry, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Other Related Companies - Porta Cara: Re: Sustainable Dev. Strategy (Tensle Khelan - rainforest Alliance), 2000 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Other Related Companies - Black Rock Forest Consortium, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Other Related Companies - the Cousteau Society (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Other Related Companies - Punta Cana, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Battle Fowler Koehler, Peter - Legal Res., Drafts + Extra Copies (RTC Matter), 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- BCSC - Mayor's Reception, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Dec 19
- Bayard Rustin Memorial Project, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Beauborg Foundation, RE: General Certificate of Incorporation, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Beauborg Foundation, RE: General Application for Exemption, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Beauborg Foundation RE: General corporate Papers and Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Beauborg Foundation, RE: General Drafts and Copies (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Beauborg foundation RE: General Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Beauborg Foundation RE: General Bank Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Beauborg foundation, RE: General Registration with Department of State (NYS), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Beauborg Foundation, RE: General Registration with A.G. - Charitable foundations Bureau (Attorney General), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Beauborg foundation, RE: General Annual IRS Tax Reports. Form 990, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Beauborg Foundation, RE: General Annual Dept. of State Tax Report NYS, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Beauborg Foundation, RE: General Annual Tax Reports for A.G. Charitable foundations Bureau, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Beauborg Foundation, RE: General Brokerage Statements Irving Trust Co., 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Beauborg Foundation RE: General Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Beauborg Foundation RE: General Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Beauborg Foundation RE: General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Bernstein, Elmer - Ameri. Fed. Of Musicians, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Bernstein, Elmer Agreement on Principles of Settlement, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Bernstein, Elmer Kennedy Center Arts Achievement Award, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- BITCO/Airport Consulting/ BNY 0951762370, 1990-1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- The Block, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- National conference CAEL/The Alliance, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Casey, Gov. Hugh, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- RE: Carriage house Center, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- the Carriage house - Center on Global Issues Articles, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- The carriage house Center on Global Issues correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues Carriage House Description, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- the Carriage house Center on Global Issues Events Correspondence, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- The Carriage house Center on Global Issues Membership Correspondence, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues Membership Lists and Contributions, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues Candlelight Awards, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues invitations, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  July 30
- the Carriage House Center on Global Issues Website Info, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- the Carriage House Center on Global Issues Corporate Documents, 2001-2003 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues Un Institutional Contract Agreement, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues New York City and the UN: A Renewed Relationship - UN Reports, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues Sustainable Developments on Global Warming (Includes UN Documents), 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- The carriage house Center on Global Issues UNCED/UN Postal Admin./ Stamps, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- The Carriage house Center on Global Issues Articles, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- The Carriage house Center on Global Issues Better World Fund., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- The Carriage house Center on Global Issues Photographs, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues Press Releases, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- C Dell corporate Documents (Box 13, Folder 24)
- C Dell: Employment Agreement w/ Ed. Staff (Box 13, Folder 25)
- C Dell: Certificate Incorporation (Box 13, Folder 26)
- C Dell: Cronkite Letter (Box 13, Folder 27)
- C Dell: Distance + Learning (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Krebs, Arlene (C Dell) RE: Distance Learning (Box 13, Folder 29)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues Digital corporate Citizenship (by Craig Warren Smith), 2002 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- The Carriage House Center on Global Issues CUNY, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- The Carriage House center, Proposal for Services by Monte Bartlett - Christo Gates (Box 13, Folder 32)
- C Dell Distance Learning, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- CNB - Restated Certificate of incorporation RE: Change of Name to Affinity Group Foundation, Inc., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- CNB/Peter Rosen RE: Toscanini, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- CNB - RE: Toscanini Project Folder 1, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- CNB - RE: Toscanini Project Folder 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the city of New York Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of New York financial information, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of New York Notice Motion for summary Judgment, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of New York Kheel Transcript, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- CNB v. Tax commission of the City of New York In Rem Installment Agreement, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- CNB v. Tax commission of the city of New York Amendment to Escrow Agreement between Center (CNB) + TCF, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of New York Stipulation of Settlement in Council on Foreign Relations v. Philip R. Michael and the Tax Commission of the city of New York et al., 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of NY Tax Documents, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of NY Automation house, Stipulation of settlement, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of NY Legal Research, 1976-1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- CNB v. Tax Commission of the City of NY miscellaneous correspondence, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- CNB/Matrix Agreement Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- CNB/Matrix Agreement, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- ABP Systems v. CNB General, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- ABP Systems v. CNB - General (Folder 2), 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- ABP Systems v CNB Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- ABP Systems V. CNB Pleadings (Box 14, Folder 22)
- ABP Systems v. CNB Agreement with CNB, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- ABP Systems v CNB Miscellaneous Information, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- ABP Systems v. CNB Financial information, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- ABP Systems v CNB IRS Returns, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- ABP Systems v CNB Deposition of Theodore W Kheel, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Liberty Elevator co. Inc. v. CNB, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Crain Communications v. CNB (Soffientini Case File), 1986 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Rosemary Enwright v. CNB-TV, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- CNB - Evaluation of artworks, 1979-1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- CNB - Exempt Forms, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- CNB, RE: TeleJapan, 1973-1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Nishimura Gallery + Rauschenberg CNB, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Center for Non-broadcast TV and Custom/Payroll, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- CNb v. AVTS Inc., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- CNB-TV v. Local AFC, Welfare and Annuity Funds (Box 14, Folder 37)
- CNB v. Neil Walsh (Box 14, Folder 38)
- (empty folder) (Box 14, Folder 39)
- CNb-TV - tenants (Box 14, Folder 40)
- CNB - Hofstra University, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- CNB - Private Satellite Network, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- CNB - NY Times, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- CNB - Peter Rosen RE: Rubinstein/Casals Program, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- CNB - School Art League, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- CNB / Tomken Management, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Manhattan Savings Bank Loan, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  Dec 18
- CNB - Title Search in Connection with MSB Mortgage (Manhattan Savings Bank), 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- CNB Mortgage Loan: Manhattan Savings Bank Mortgage, Center for Non-Broadcast TV 06035-006 RE: Sale of Automation House (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Corporate Documents CNB - RE: Chemical Bank's mortgage, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- CNB - TV: TFC National properties, Inc., Mortgage, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  Dec.
- Corporate Documents CNB - RE: State + City Tax Exempt Status, 1965-1986 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- CNB - TV, Upgrading and Maintenance of electrical System (Plant), 1976-1982 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Warranties (RE: EBCO - Water Cooler) CNB-TV (General), 1979 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Xerox, CNB-TV, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Zoning - 50 East 69 St., CNB-TV General, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- CNB - Chuff Insurance statements, 1977-1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- CNB-TV Flash Report, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- New York Telephone CNB-TV, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- CNB - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- CNB - Project Metro-Link - Fed. Planning Assistance, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- R.O.C.I. CNB-TV General File, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Resumes CNB - William Sobel, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- CNB - Correspondence File re: Financial Obligations, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- CNB - Misc. Financial Center for Non-Broadcast Television, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- CNB - Misc. Financial, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Financial Reports CNB, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- CNB-TV 1980 Financial Reports (Box 15, Folder 12)
- financial Reports CNB, 1962-1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- CNB-TV (Lien - Federal Tax), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- CNB (Center Non-Broadcast Television) + Custom Broadcast Networking - Gen. Ledger + Gen. Journal, 1988-1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- CNB (Center for Non-Broadcast Television) + Custom Network Broadcasting - Gen. Ledger + Gen. journal, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- CNB (Center for Non-Broadcast TV)/Custom Broadcasting Network - Gen. Ledger + GenJournal, 1985-1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Adjustments for General journal CNB, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- CNB - Financial Statements + Worksheets, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 19)